[
    {
        "front": "となり",
        "back": "Next to",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぎ",
        "back": "Keys",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "わたしたち",
        "back": "We, us",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "あなた",
        "back": "You (informal)",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいしゃいん",
        "back": "Company Employee",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃいん",
        "back": "Company Employee",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎんこういん",
        "back": "Bank Employee",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "いしゃ",
        "back": "Doctor",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがく",
        "back": "University",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "びょういん",
        "back": "Hospital",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "びよういん",
        "back": "Beauty Parlor",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "くん",
        "back": "Equivalent to san (Used for younger ones)",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんき",
        "back": "Electricity",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんきやさん",
        "back": "Electronic showroom",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "おなまえ",
        "back": "(Your) Name",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "へや",
        "back": "Room",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "タバコ",
        "back": "Ciggarette",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "すいます",
        "back": "To smoke, to inhale",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちがいます",
        "back": "To differ, its different",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "びじゅつかん",
        "back": "Art museum",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうびんきょく",
        "back": "Post Office",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "スーパー",
        "back": "Supermarket",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "とります",
        "back": "To take, To pass",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "あいます",
        "back": "To meet",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "みせ",
        "back": "Shop",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅくだい",
        "back": "Homework",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいたい",
        "back": "Almost",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "よく",
        "back": "Often",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "すこし",
        "back": "Little",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜんぜん",
        "back": "Not at all",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいかつ",
        "back": "Lifestyle, Daily life",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どっな",
        "back": "What kind of",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "やきゅう",
        "back": "Baseball game",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "うた",
        "back": "Song",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "うたいます",
        "back": "To sing",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "え",
        "back": "Painting",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "やくそく",
        "back": "Promise",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "はやく",
        "back": "Quickly",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "おそく",
        "back": "Late",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "こども",
        "back": "Child, Children",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "はこ",
        "back": "Box",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃしん",
        "back": "Photograph",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "もの",
        "back": "Things",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "そのほか",
        "back": "Besides, Other than this",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "~や ~や ~など",
        "back": "~, ~, ~etc.",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいへん",
        "back": "Hard, tiresome",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "おおい",
        "back": "Large number",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "いろいろ",
        "back": "Various\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "より",
        "back": "Compared to",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ずっと",
        "back": "By far (While comparing)",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "くうこう",
        "back": "Airport",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんど",
        "back": "Next",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "だれ / どなた",
        "back": "Who",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんさい / おいくつ",
        "back": "How Old",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "なん / なに",
        "back": "What",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どこ / どちら",
        "back": "Where",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "いくら",
        "back": "How much (Money)",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつ",
        "back": "When",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どう / どうやって",
        "back": "How",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どっな",
        "back": "What kind of",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうして",
        "back": "Why",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どれ / どの",
        "back": "Which",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "いくつ",
        "back": "How many",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どのくらい",
        "back": "How long",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "どちら",
        "back": "Which (option)",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "なぜ",
        "back": "Why (polite)",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "うみ",
        "back": "Sea, Ocean",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    },
    {
        "front": "やま",
        "back": "Mountain",
        "chapter": "N5 C11"
    }
]